Hug him!
抱一个
Congrats!
恭喜 恭喜
Hug him! Hug him!
抱一个 抱一个 抱一个
I...Can't breathe...
喘喘 喘不上
Can't breathe...
喘不上气了
So difficult!
好难
Get over there, there!
那边 那边
What's this?
这 这什么
What is it?
这什么
I think Class 5 is outstanding.
我觉得五班特别优秀
Mr. Zhao, what's wrong?
赵老师 你怎么了
I'm fine.
没事 没事 没事
I'm fine, Ms. Fang.
没事 方老师
I just,
我啊
seeing these students,
就是看到这帮学生
I just think,
就觉得
it's great to be young.
年轻真好
I think I'm young as well.
我觉得我挺年轻的啊
That's true.
那倒也是
Actually, I've been meaning to ask you.
其实我一直想问你
Ms. Fang, do you have a boyfriend?
方老师 你有男朋友吗
Boyfriend?
男朋友
I go to school everyday,
我这每天上学的时候
to teach them.
得陪他们上课
Finally, there's a weekend,
好不容易有个周末吧
and I got dragged here for training.
你看 被拉过来拉练了
Do you really think I've got time
你觉得我有时间
to date anyone?
谈恋爱吗
So,
那
Ms. Fang, what is your
方老师喜欢
favourite type?
什么类型的呀
I mean,
我 我是想问
what type of guy
你喜欢什么类型的
are you into?
男生
What type am I into?
我喜欢什么类型的
I really haven't thought about it.
这我还真没想过
I think it's about feeling.
我觉得这个看感觉吧
But,
但我
regarding the type I don't like,
我不喜欢什么类型的
I'm quite clear about it.
我倒是很明确
So what type
那你不喜欢
don't you like?
什么类型的呀
I don't like
我不喜欢
guys who wear sportswear every day.
每天穿运动装的
Coach, bye-bye.
教练 拜拜
Bye!
拜拜
See ya, instructor!
拜拜教官
Don't cause
回去少惹
any trouble for Ms. Fang, OK?
你们方老师生气啊
OK.
好
Ms. Fang,
方老师
please visit us when you got time.
有空常回来看看
OK.
好
Thanks for your help,
谢谢你这些天的照顾
instructor.
吴教官
Don't mention it.
跟我客气什么呀
Ms. Fang!
方老师
Hey.
哎
Let's go on the same bus.
待会儿我跟你们车走吧
Alright.
行
Mr. Zhao.
赵老师
Mr. Wu,
吴教官
thanks for your hospitality.
给你们添麻烦了
No problem.
不麻烦
Come and visit us.
有空常回来玩
Sure.
一言为定
You should get going.
走吧
See you!
再见
Bye.
拜拜
How do I look, Ms. Fang?
怎么样 方老师
I think...
我觉得
You should stick to wearing sportswear.
你还是穿运动衫吧
I don't look good in this?
不帅吗
It seems this training
看来这次拉练
really wore them out.
真是给他们累着了
They're all asleep.
一个个都睡了
Yeah.
是啊
Ms. Fang.
方老师
Huh?
嗯
This really doesn't look good?
这 真的不帅吗
What?
什么
This whole...
这
Ah.
啊
It...It's OK.
还 还行
Right?
是吧
I thought it was ok too.
我也觉得还行
I've spent some time picking it out.
挑了半天呢
Back then, the future
那个时候的我们
seemed so distant it had no shape.
未来遥远得像没有形状
Every day's troubles were
每天的烦恼
only homework and the people around us.
只剩下作业和身边的人
Even if the day before
即使头一天
we argued until we were red in the face,
争吵到面红耳赤
we could make up
也能在几句道歉中
after a few apologies.
重归于好
Maybe
或许
this is the privilege of youth.
这就是少年的特权吧
Guys,
同学们
your physical test
咱们班这一次
results are out.
体测的成绩出来了
This time
这次体测呢
everyone's shown significant improvement.
大家进步都非常的明显
Most of you
我们班大部分同学
have passed.
都已经及格了
This proves that our last training
证明咱们上一次的拉练
was very effective.
效果还是非常显著的
You all did very well.
大家都非常不错啊
So, remember,
所以说呢
it's important to work out
平时还是要在学习之余
in addition to your studies.
注意锻炼
Alright?
好吧
Yes, ma'am!
好
Chen Luyang, Ling Dong,
陈璐阳 凌冬
you two,
你们两个
go to the office.
去下老师办公室
Mr. Guo is looking for you.
郭老师找
- OK - Xu Mengyu,
好 徐梦予
come up and post
你上来把这个成绩单
this score sheet.
贴一下
OK.
好
Over there.
贴那儿就行
Alright,
我说一下啊
although many of you
虽然咱班这次
have passed this time,
及格的同学有很多
there are still some
可是还有一部分同学
who have not.
是不及格的
I still hope
老师还是希望
that you could spend some time
在学习之余
working out
你们可以多多运动
when you are free,
多多锻炼
oK?
好吧
Yes, ma'am!
好
Alright, go ahead and
行 那你们一会儿
check your scores.
自己看一下成绩单
Yes, ma'am.
好
Mr. Guo.
郭老师
Hello, Mr. Guo.
郭老师好
For the national physics competition,
这一次全国物理大赛
the school has decided
学校决定
to let you two represent the school
让你们两个代表学校
and compete in Jing City.
去京市参赛
The results of this competition
这次的成绩
concern not only your future
不光事关你们的前途
but also the honor of our school.
也代表咱们学校的荣誉
Ms. Fang and I will take you there then.
到时候我和方老师带队
Do your best,
你们要好好发挥
alright?
加油
Don't worry, Mr. Guo,
放心吧 郭老师
I will definitely give my best.
到时候我肯定好好考
Sir,
那老师
if there's nothing else,
没什么事
I'm going back then.
我就先回班里了
One sec,
别急
the days after your competition
你们比赛结束的那几天
happen to be Jing University's open days.
正好是京大开放日
There will be a lecture by Professor Yang.
到时候有杨教授的讲座
You can check it out if you're interested.
你们有兴趣可以去听听
These days,
这些天呢
the physics room will be open for you.
物理教室为你们开放
If you have any questions,
有什么问题
feel free to ask me anytime.
你们可以随时来找我
Do you know if
你们知不知道
Mr. Guo asked Ling Dong and Chen Luoyang
郭老师找凌冬和陈璐阳
to represent the entire school
是不是叫他们代表全校
in the national physics competition?
参加全国物理竞赛啊
There's no doubt about it.
这还能有什么悬念啊
It must be it.
肯定是呗
Participating in such competitions
一般参加这种比赛
and winning a place
拿了名次
may earn you credits for entering college.
高考是可以加分的
Extra credits?
加分
For real?
真的
Yeah.
对啊
Hey, they're already top students
你说说
and still getting extra credits.
都已经是学神了还加分
What about us
像我们这种普通人
ordinary people?
怎么办呀
Yeah.
对啊
But there's only
不过第一名
one first place.
好像只有一位
That's probably Ling Dong.
那估计就是凌冬了
I feel sorry for Chen Luyang.
陈璐阳也太可怜了吧
As long as there's Ling Dong,
只要有凌冬在
he'll always be the eternal second place.
他永远都是千年老二
Hi, Chen Luyang.
班长
That one, right?
那个是吗
Seems like it.
好像是啊
That's good.
挺好的
It's all about representing our school.
反正都是代表学校出战
It doesn't matter who's first or second.
不分一二
You're right.
对对对
Right.
对
Let's go back to the classroom.
走走走 回教室
Let's go.
走走走
What did Mr. Guo want with you?
郭老师找你干嘛去了
He said I should participate
老师说让我参加
in the national physics competition.
全国的物理竞赛
Oh.
哦
Jing University Open Days?
京大开放日
Ling Dong,
凌冬
are you planning to go there?
你要去京大开放日啊
What's it about? Is it fun?
这什么日子 好玩吗
It's an event Jing University holds.
就是京大为了招生
It's going to be a week
会举办为期一周的
to attract new students.
开放日
I heard their Department of Fine Arts
听说他们美术系
has an art exhibition every year.
每年都会举办画展
I'd really love to go.
我也好想去啊
If you want to go, we can just go.
想去我们就去呗
I need to prepare for the competition.
我要备赛
I might not have time.
不一定有时间
That's true.
也是
Plus, this event is super popular.
而且这个开放日特别火
Even though they distribute
虽然他们每年
tickets every year,
会定期发放门票
the number of people who go there
但是慕名而去的人
is just too large.
真的太多了
Tickets are incredibly hard to get.
可谓是一票难求
Is that so?
还有门坎儿
Chen Luyang, are you OK?
陈璐阳 你怎么了
Qingtian,
晴天
I'm fine.
我没事啊
You look
我看你的脸色
a bit pale.
有点不太好
Is it because you've been
是不是因为
preparing for the physics competition
最近要准备物理竞赛
and didn't get enough sleep?
没休息好
I am feeling a bit of stressed,
确实有点压力
but it's oK.
但没关系
Don't worry about me.
你不用担心我
Have a lollipop.
吃颗棒棒糖吧
Whenever I'm under a lot of pressure,
我每次压力大的时候
I'll just have a lollipop.
就吃棒棒糖
It makes me feel like everything's better.
觉得世界都美好了
Thank you.
谢谢
No problem.
不用谢
There's nothing
没有什么是一根棒棒糖
that a lollipop can't fix.
解决不了的事情
If there is, then have two.
如果有就两根
Goodbye, ma'am!
老师再见
Goodbye, guys.
同学们再见
Let's all go to the cafeteria.
我们一起去食堂吧
Let's go.
走吧
Nah, I'm not going.
哎呦 我不去了
You have to eat.
不吃饭怎么行啊
Food is as vital to people
人是铁饭是钢
as steel is to machines.
你这样下去
I have no appetite.
我没胃口
You guys go ahead.
你们先去吧
Forget it,
算了 算了 算了
he's already
他现在已经进入了
in his maniac mode.
变态模式了
Mere mortals won't be able to understand.
我们这些凡人是理解不了
Let's go eat.
咱们先去吃吧
We'll bring him food.
给他带饭
Come on, we'll bring him food.
走了 给他带饭
Alright, alright,
好了 好了 好了
let's go.
走了
Dear lord,
天哪
did you see the video yesterday?
你看昨天热搜视频没有
Jia was super-hot!
嘉哥真的太帅了
Yeah, yeah.
看了
That voice was amazing, you know?
那嗓音绝了你知道吗
It was fantastic!
太棒了
I got goosebumps, seriously!
我都紧张了 真的是
Yeah.
对呀对呀
That vibrato is really something.
那转音真是
Let's go, Jinghui!
走啊 灰哥
Let's shoot some hoops!
打球去
That's it for today's class.
今天的课就讲到这里
Take some time to take it all in.
大家好好消化一下
Dismissed.
下课
Stand up.
起立
Goodbye, sir.
老师再见
Nah, I can't, sitting in the same room
不行 不行
with him is too stressful.
跟他在一起做题太压抑了
Ling Dong, you...
凌冬 你
Do you know what the dieticians say?
你知不知道专家说过
If you don't eat properly,
如果不好好吃饭
it will impact your intelligence.
是会影响智力
If you want to win the competition,
如果你想要考第一
you've got to eat.
必须要吃饭
They also say
专家还说过
you can't drink freshly boiled water.
不能喝开水呢
Why is that?
为什么
Because it's hot.
因为烫嘴
Stop being so contrary with me.
你别跟我抬杠啊
Anyway, now
反正现在
you have to eat.
你必须给我吃了
Just eat it.
你赶紧把它吃进去就行
OK, oK.
我吃 我吃
Health is of utmost importance,
身体是革命的本钱
so you must eat properly.
所以一定要好好吃饭
I know how to solve it now.
我知道解法了
Give it back.
本给我
Practice is one thing,
做题归做题
you can't neglect food and sleep.
你不能废寝忘食啊
You've got to eat!
你得一块吃
Sorry.
对不起
This the last time I brought you food.
就这一次了
Hey, why are you still here?
班长 你怎么还没回家
What?
干嘛
Any chance you have more lollipops?
还有糖吗
This is the last piece I have.
就剩一颗了
But looks like you could use a pick-me-up,
不过看你这么可怜
so it's yours.
就给你了
Chen Luyang,
班长
you seem a bit off lately, what's up?
话说你最近到底怎么了
It's nothing, really.
其实没什么事
Take this, it's for you.
这个送给你
The Qingtian (sunny) doll.
晴天娃娃
It's like having
见到它
Xia Qingtian right with you.
就如见到夏晴天
But it's yours.
可是这是你的
Let it be a
它会代替我
source of strength for you.
赐给你力量的
Best of luck with the physics competition!
物理竞赛加油
Thanks.
谢谢
Ling Dong!
凌冬
Ling Dong, bad news!
凌冬 不好了
What's the matter? What's going on?
怎么 怎么了
It's Lan Jinghui, Lan Jinghui...
兰靖灰 兰靖灰他
Take a breath and tell me what happened.
你慢慢说兰靖灰怎么了
He got into a conflict
兰靖灰他在校外
with someone off-campus.
跟人起冲突了
Where is he now?
哪儿呢
I'm sorry, Ling Dong.
对不起 凌冬
I lied to you.
我跟你说谎了
Hey,
不是
I haven't finished a problem yet.
我还有道题没做完
You're already here, so stay a while.
来都来了 别走了
Lan Jinghui!
兰靖灰
Seriously,
不是
Xiaohua,
小画
why are you picking up his bad habits?
你怎么跟他学坏了啊
Don't be mad at her.
你别怪她
It was my idea.
这是我的主意
Have a seat.
坐下
You've been studying
这不是看你这几天
so hard these
没日没夜的学习
past few days.
太辛苦了吗
You've lost weight from not eating enough.
人都饿瘦了
Look,
来
I've prepared this just for you,
特意为你准备的
a feast to nourish your brain.
补脑全席
You're off to the capital tomorrow, right?
明天你不是要去京市嘛
Consider this meal a farewell from bro.
这顿就当哥给你送行了
Bro?
哥
aren't you getting
你这个辈分
our relationship a bit mixed up?
是不是有点乱呀
It's close enough.
差不多嘛
Plus, it's about eating the right foods.
而且以形补形
Try these,
尝尝我特地
I ordered them just for you:
为你点的这个
pig brain soup,
清汤猪脑
egg-fried pig brain,
蛋炒猪脑
braised pig brain,
红烧猪脑
pig brain stew,
水煮猪脑
grilled pig brain,
碳烤猪脑
and fish stew.
还有水煮鱼
That's just right.
那正好
You should eat more.
你更得多吃点
It's all about eating the right foods.
以形补形
Here.
来
Thanks (screw you).
谢谢你啊
I'm the one being grateful (screw you).
我谢谢你啊
It's me, Ms. Fang!
是我呀 方老师
Sorry, Mr. Zhao!
对不起啊 赵老师
My apologies,
对不起 对不起
are you alright?
没事吧
I'm oK, I'm oK.
没事 没事
What brings you here?
你 你怎么来了
Where's Mr. Guo?
郭老师呢
I'll be accompanying you to Jing City.
我跟你们一块去京市
Mr. Guo had a family issue,
郭老师临时家里有事儿
so Mr. Zhang asked me to go with you.
主任就派我来了
I'm really sorry for what I did.
刚刚真的对不起啊
It's fine.
没事儿
Shall we
那
go get our boarding pass for the train?
要不咱先去换高铁票
Sure.
好
Let's go.
那走吧
Ms. Fang, that was
方老师的身手
quite some impressive move back there.
真是太好了
Surprise!
惊喜
What are you all doing here?
你们怎么来了
We...
我们
Of course
我们当然
are off to have fun in Jing City.
是要去京市玩了
It's the May Day long vacation,
这不五一长假嘛
and Xiaohua's never been to the city.
正好我徒弟没有去过京市
So, I thought
然后呢
I'd take her to broaden her horizons,
我想去带她见见世面
right?
对不对
Exactly, exactly.
对对对
And you, Qingtian?
你呢 晴天
Why are you here?
你怎么来了
Well, I'm obviously
我当然
going to the city's food festival
是要去京市参加美食节
to hit up all the trendy spots.
打卡所有的网红店了
Here you go.
给你
Thanks, Qingtian.
谢谢晴天
Prof. Yang's seminar at Jing University?
京大物理讲座杨教授
What's the matter?
怎么了
Nothing.
没怎么了啊
You've been holding that the whole time.
我就看你一直拿着
Just curious.
我看一眼
You're not really into this, are you?
你不会对这个感兴趣吧
Nah. Just a peek.
没什么 我就随便看看
Ling Dong.
凌冬
Ms. Fang.
方老师
Mr. Zhao.
赵老师
Why are you here?
你们俩怎么来了
We...
我们
I...
我我我
Just going to Jing City for some fun.
我们 我们去京市玩
All three of you?
你们仨都去玩啊
Right.
对对对
Are your parents cool
那你们出去玩儿
with this?
家长知道吗
Yeah,
知道
they're
不仅知道
totally on board.
而且安排还特别妥当
Got it all sorted out.
什么都管了
Let's go.
走吧
Yeah?
是吗
We're gonna miss the train
如果我们再不出发
if we don't move.
时间来不及了
Okay.
行
Listen up,
我跟你们说啊
you can enjoy yourselves,
你去玩可以啊
but I gotta
但有一点
make one thing clear.
我得跟你们说清楚
Don't mess around.
去了以后别捣乱
If I catch wind of
一旦我发现
any shenanigans,
你们几个捣乱
I'll send you back straight away.
我立马给你们遣返回来
Let's go.
走吧 走吧
Go.
出发
Go get the tickets!
取票去啦
Go, chop-chop.
走走走 快快快
We gotta hurry.
时间不够了
How's it?
怎么样
That dome ceiling and green scenery
欧陆穹顶 生态大堂
make the air
有没有觉得进到这里
feel cleaner, huh?
空气都变得清新了些许
It's refreshing.
是挺清新的
But kinda chilly.
就是有点冷
Yeah?
是吗
Whoa,
你们看
check out those peacocks.
这儿还有两只孔雀
Gorgeous!
好好看啊
Yeah.
真的
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
So this is the hotel
这就是你说
you said you got us?
你给我们安排的酒店啊
Yep.
没错
Pretty awesome, huh?
是不是非常好
Nope.
不怎么样
Firstly, I'm here on a business trip,
首先第一我是来出差的
and they're here to study for exams.
他们俩是来备考的
Only the three of you
就只有你们三个人
are here
是轻装上阵
just for leisure.
过来旅游的
This hotel's way
住这么好的酒店
too fancy for us.
你觉得合适吗
Besides,
再说了
we don't have the budget for it.
我们也没有这个预算
Ms. Fang.
方老师
I know, I got it.
我明白了 我知道
But this hotel
但是这家京市的酒店
has close
跟我爸有着
business ties with my dad.
非常密切的商务来往
So we're getting
我们能拿到的价格是
a sweet deal.
低于团购价的最低价格
It's like
跟普通的这个经济啊
a budget hotel,
快捷连锁酒店
but nicer.
没什么区别
And I'm sure
而且其次呢
you math and
想必二位数学天才
physics geniuses
物理天才
are exhausted,
一定相当地劳累了
you need some rest
所以我们需要一个这样
in a chill spot.
安静优雅的地方来休息
Am I right?
你说对不对
Yes, right.
对啊 对啊
Ms. Fang.
方老师
Let's just stay here.
咱们就住这儿吧
You sure it's within budget?
你确定不超预算
Absolutely.
一分不超
Let me be clear,
我丑话说前面啊
since I brought you guys out,
我既然把你们带出来了
I gotta keep tabs on you.
我就得对你们负责任
If you're going out,
必须得
keep me in the loop,
随时跟我保持联系
alright?
让我知道你们的行踪
No problem.
没问题
And
还有
back to the hotel
晚上八点钟之前
by 8 sharp,
必须回酒店
hear me?
听见没
And
另外
remember,
这次呢
our main purpose here
我们主要是来
is to support Ling Dong and Chen Luyang.
陪凌冬和陈璐阳备考的
So
所以为了
without my permission,
给他们提供一个安静的
don't step
备考环境
near their rooms
没有我的允许
to give them
你们不许靠近
a peaceful study environment.
陈璐阳和凌冬房间半步
Hear me?
听见了吗
Especially you.
尤其是你
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
No problem.
没问题
Let's go check in.
我们先去办理入住
Let's go.
走
Wait, wait.
等等 等等
It's so cute.
这也太可爱了吧
It looks like you, doesn't it?
你不觉得这个很像你吗
Me?
有吗
Give me a grin.
你笑一个
Exactly the same.
可以说是一模一样
Yeah?
是吧
Yeah.
特像
Isn't it Nerd Ling?
这不凌大呆子吗
You're right.
你一说还真是
You've got his vibe down pat.
你这简直模仿到了精髓
Yeah?
是吧 是吧
Right.
是不是
And this is Ma Yiming.
还有马一鸣
Ma Yiming.
马一鸣
Spot on.
太像了
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
This is you.
这是你吧
Like a clone.
一模一样
Channel your inner doll.
你快模仿一下
You got it.
真的是哎
Am I really like that?
我有这样吗
Yup, spot on.
你就是这样
Not even close.
根本就不像好不好
It's you.
太像了
Down to a T.
兰靖灰本灰
Which one's my doppelganger?
那哪个是我啊
You've all got yours.
你们都有了
I think this one looks a lot like you.
我觉得这个就挺像你
Yeah, this is the one.
对 这个像
Am I really this cute?
我有这么可爱吗
Totally.
有
It's too loud!
吵死了
Unbearable!
怎么这么吵啊
Dancing all night
晚上跳就算了
and now during the day?
白天还要跳
I'm over it.
烦死了
It's getting late.
这都几点了
Where is he?
他怎么还不来啊
Slower
怎么比我们
than snails.
两个女孩都慢啊
Sleep in or what?
他是不是睡过头了
Calling him now.
我给他打个电话
It's him.
来了 来了
Sorry I'm late.
来晚了
What took you so long?
你怎么才下来呀
I overslept.
起晚了
We got back
昨天咱们不是
early last night.
回来得挺早的嘛
You're still tired?
你怎么看起来还是这么困
I was up all night on Zelda.
昨晚通宵打游戏来着
So addictive.
塞尔达真的很上头
Those horse-men are brutal.
半人马非常难打
I don't get it.
听不懂
Let's move.
快走吧
Or we'll miss breakfast.
再晚吃不了早饭了
Okay.
走
Let's go.
走吧 走吧
Yeah.
走吧
Ms. Fang.
方老师
We got a bit
你说咱是不是
carried away, huh?
买得有点多呀
Can we really finish all this?
这吃得了吗
Nah, just some veggies.
不多呀 都是些菜啊
They're studying
而且他们俩不是
for exams,
马上要考试了嘛
but eating takeout all the time
这几天都是吃的外卖
which is heavy on oil and salt.
重油重盐的
They need these greens.
所以我这不是多买点菜
So I'm gonna whip up
想着晚上亲自下厨
something good tonight.
给他们做点好吃的嘛
Let's see.
我看看还
What else do we need?
缺点什么呀
You catch a cold?
你怎么了 感冒了
I think
我估计是这个
the hotel AC's blasting
酒店空调开得太大了
gave me a chill.
有点着凉
Here, cold instant granules.
来 感冒药给你
Go back and dissolve it in water.
回去赶紧吃了
Appreciate the concern,
谢谢方老师
thanks.
这么关心我
It's not like that.
我不是关心你
It's just, you know,
这不是现在是
a crucial time.
关键时刻吗
Don't give
别把这感冒
the students your cold.
传染给凌冬跟陈璐阳了
Don't worry, I won't.
你放心 肯定不会的
Okay.
行
Right.
对了
Need some pork ribs.
我还得再去买点排骨
Hold on a sec.
你等我一下啊
I'll go, be right back.
我去 等我一下啊
Alright, I want spareribs.
那行 要小排啊
Yeah, got it.
好嘞 好嘞
Miss.
小姑娘
You're gonna cook all this?
你这是买菜做饭吗
Yeah.
对 阿姨
Looks like you're not just pretty,
看来你上得厅堂
but also a fantastic cook.
下得厨房
Miss.
姑娘
What do you do for work?
你是做什么工作的
I'm a high school teacher.
我是高中老师
It's nice.
当老师好啊
My son's
阿姨家有个儿子
tall
个高腿长
and handsome.
人也长得很帅
But he's been busy with work.
就是工作太忙了
So he's still single.
现在没找对象
Maybe you two can hit it off?
要不你们俩认识认识
Friend me.
你加我 扫我
Let's go.
走吧
The kids are waiting for us.
孩子们还在家里等着呢
What? Miss.
不会吧 姑娘
You look so young,
你 你看起来年纪轻轻
got kids already?
怎么会有孩子啊
She's youthful-looking,
阿姨 她显小
but we're parents of five already.
我们都五个孩子了
Wow, can't tell at all.
看不出来 看不出来
Bye.
再见 阿姨
Let's go.
走了
Five kids already?
你可真敢说
Seriously?
不是
That's crazy talk.
怎么就五个孩子了
Two in books,
两个在备考呢
three out playing.
另外三个去玩了
Makes five, right?
这不是五个吗
Just trying to
我这也是急中生智
save the day here.
给你解围呢嘛
Well...
那
What if I do wanna friend her?
万一我想认识人家呢
Well... Seen Lan and the girls?
那什么 兰靖灰他们呢
Haven't
我今儿
caught sight all day.
一天没看见他们了
They hit you up?
给你打电话了吗
Nope.
没有
Quick, call them up.
你赶紧给他们打个电话
Chill, they're fine.
你放心 肯定丢不了
Alright.
行行行
Probably having a blast somewhere.
不定跟哪儿正玩得嗨呢
Let me.
我来 我来 我来
Okay.
行
Well.
那个 你记得
Tell them to
待会儿给他们打电话
come back for dinner
让他们晚上回来吃饭
and keep it early.
别让他们回来的太晚了
Soup's on.
汤来喽
Here.
来啦
Ms. Fang
这是你们方老师
whipped these up
借酒店厨房
in the hotel kitchen.
亲自下厨做的
Dig in while hot.
趁热吃啊
Crush that exam tomorrow.
明天好好考
Thank you, Ms. Fang.
谢谢方老师
Thanks, Ms. Fang.
谢方老师
Here, Luyang.
来 陈璐阳
Delicious!
真好吃
You guys haven't
我看你们呀
been eating properly lately.
最近都没怎么好好吃饭
Help yourselves.
来 赶紧吃啊
Here, Ms. Fang.
来 方老师
I've been eating pretty well these days,
我这几天吃得还不错
thanks for the late-night noms, Ms. Fang.
谢谢方老师每天的夜宵
Late-night noms?
夜宵
What?
有吗
But I
我没有给你
didn't.
每天送夜宵啊
Ms. Fang.
方老师
Xiaohua, Qingtian.
小画 晴天
Come and sit.
快来坐下
Ms. Fang.
方老师
You made all of this?
这些都是你做的呀
Looks amazing.
看起来好好吃啊
Quick, dig in!
快 赶快吃一点
Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢
Right.
对了
Just you two?
怎么就你们俩回来了
Where's Lan?
兰靖灰呢
Isn't he back yet?
他没回来吗
Lan said he had business,
他说有事先回酒店了
so he bailed early.
就提前走了
Give him a ring and see what's up.
你给他打个电话问问
Help yourself.
吃啊
Excuse me.
你们先吃啊
Ms. Fang.
方老师
This is seriously good eating!
你做的菜太好吃了
Yeah?
是吗
Anytime you're hungry,
那以后你想吃饭
just swing by my place,
就到方老师家来
I'll whip up something tasty.
方老师做给你吃
Have some more.
多吃点啊
You guys fill up?
你们俩吃饱了吗
Okay.
行
Hit the hay
那你们今天
don't burn the midnight oil.
晚上别复习太晚了
Good luck on
明天就要考试了
the exam tomorrow,
老师希望你们
hope you ace it!
能够考一个好的成绩
Alright, go now.
那你们快回去吧
Gonna have another bite.
我再吃一会儿
Yeah, Qingtian, fill your belly.
那你多吃点 晴天
Go.
去吧
Bye.
老师再见
Good night.
好好休息
Thanks.
谢谢老师
Bye.
拜拜
Good night.
早点休息
Qingtian,  what's
晴天 你平时
your favorite dish?
都喜欢吃什么菜啊
I'm not picky.
我没有不喜欢吃的
What took you
你打个电话
so long on the phone?
怎么打那么久啊
I hit up his room,
我刚刚去房间找他了
no one there.
没在
Scoured
我又去酒店楼下
the hotel,
转了一圈
still missing.
也没有
Where could he be?
这小子去哪儿了
Phone's off the hook too.
这电话也不接
Give me your phone, I'll call him.
你电话给我 我来打
Okay.
行
I knew he would cause trouble
我就知道这小子出来
as soon as he stepped out.
肯定不会给我省心
Any weird
他这两天
behavior from him lately?
有什么异样没有啊
Nah, doesn't look like it.
好像没有
I'm getting a weird vibe from him.
我倒觉得他有点不对劲
What did he mention before taking off?
他走之前说什么了吗
Just that he's heading back.
他就说他先回酒店
His phone's dead.
电话也关机了
Now, finish up your food and
这样 你们俩接着吃
then wait for him in the lobby.
吃完以后去房间等着
If Lan shows up,
要是兰靖灰回来的话
let me know.
你们赶紧通知我
Zhao Yun, forget the phone calls,
赵云 你别打电话了
let's hit the streets.
咱俩出去找
Yeah.
走
Okay.
好
We're leaving now,
我俩先走了啊
keep me posted
他回来
if he shows up.
一定赶紧通知我啊
Okay.
好
Qingtian, forget the food,
晴天 咱们也别吃了
hurry to the lobby.
我们赶紧回房间
So that if Lan pops up,
万一兰靖灰回来了
we can inform Ms. Fang right away.
我们好通知方老师
Okay.
走
Why hasn't he come back yet?
怎么还不回来啊
Xiaohua.
小画
Xiaohua. Qingtian.
小画 晴天
What are you guys doing here?
你们在这儿干嘛啊
We... Nothing.
我们 没干什么呀
Just chatting.
我们就是在闲聊
We're just bored
我们就是太无聊了
and taking a stroll around.
在这儿遛弯
Where's Lan?
兰靖灰呢
Isn't he back yet?
他还没回来
He's out getting something, probably.
他去买东西了吧 应该
Get what?
他买什么东西啊
Where'd he go?
他去哪儿买东西了
He...
去
I'll go look for him.
我去找他
Lan is
兰靖灰他
missing.
不见了
What?
什么
Alright.
来
A special brain-boosting feast
特意为你准备的
prepared just for you.
补脑全席
Clear Soup Pig Brain.
清汤猪脑
Scrambled Egg with Pig Brain.
蛋炒猪脑
Braised Pig Brain in Soy Sauce.
红烧猪脑
Boiled Pig Brain.
水煮猪脑
Charcoal-Grilled Pig Brain.
碳烤猪脑
The pig brain
这个猪脑花
really messed up my stomach.
劲儿太大了吧
Hope it doesn't affect the nerd.
呆子不会也中招吧
Hey,
我说你
how are you feeling after the meal?
吃完饭肚子有没有事儿
I'm fine.
没事儿啊
Good then.
没事儿就好
Gonna wipe the plate clean.
我要全部吃光
Hey guys, let's all perk up
同学们都打起精神来啊
and get ready for the exam.
一会儿准备考试
Mam, my stomach's killing me.
老师 我肚子疼得厉害
I gotta hit the loo.
我 我想去个厕所
Hope it won't
不会跟当初
give him the runs the next day
那个鲤鱼一样吧
like what that carp did to me.
隔天发作
Hello, Xiaohua?
喂 徒弟啊
It's me.
对对对
I gotta tell you something right now,
我有一件十万火急的事
it's very urgent.
要立马通知你